Let's go,
let's try to succeed there.
The Low Rider
is a Little higher.
thank you,
Did you see the name?
forgiveness is Maria Eduarda
Maria who is a manager here.
manager, I will,
can be
all right.
jané, is the following,
I ordered a coffee.
I'm not that person to talk about complaining
nothing no.
by the way,
it's wonderful,
my congratulations,
I even scared.
is repairing your service
and the layout of that place is.
it's exactly what i'm looking for
for positioning my brand.
and I work with a line of craft Passengers
made with high quality products
and i wanted to leave it to you
to collect a box with a sample of the products,
can let yes,
It is fine?
interested hunting?
leave my silence
then I sit in touch.
this one o
for you,
I hope you like it.
thank you
dear,
with 1 bunch of box here now
and that's it,
find some other tomb now
but 1,
in case you like,
I just ask you to give the feedback,
I thank you.
I do my darling
to work.
Man,
some tribe call me to place the Passengers,
You know?
I'm betting all the chips for this idea to work.
now i need to hope for something
contact me
and then wait
has no way.
Is it on?
so that was the tenth
build 1 business.
tamo together.
until tomorrow.
it was!